Ninety percent of startups fail.
Three hundred and seventy thousand Australian businesses closed last year.
Ninety-seven billion dollars in AI funding. Ninety percent still fail.
The gap: AI builds products. Nothing builds businesses.
Hi, I'm Long from BlockID.au.
I've seen founders build amazing AI products, then struggle to value them, split equity fairly, or get investor-ready.
We built the platform that fixes this -- from day one.
Australian founders face three critical problems.
One -- how much is my idea worth? A manual valuation costs five thousand to fifty thousand dollars and takes weeks. We do it with AI in sixty seconds, from one dollar.
Two -- how do I split equity? Forty-two percent of co-founder disputes destroy startups. Our calculator makes it fair and transparent.
Three -- how do I get investor-ready? Data rooms take weeks to prepare. Our evidence vault auto-scores your readiness.
Let me show you how BlockID works.
You describe your startup in plain text -- your idea, your team, your traction.
Our AI analyzes it across eight dimensions -- market, product, traction, team, cap table, investor readiness, legal, and vision.
In under sixty seconds, you get your Startup Value Index -- a real, evidence-backed score.
Plus a ten-page report with market research, competitor analysis, and business model evaluation.
But we don't just give you a number. Every recommendation links directly to a tool.
Click 'Build your cap table' and the equity calculator opens.
Set your founder split, co-founder allocation, and ESOP pool. The moment you complete it, your SVI auto-rescores.
One thirty-eight becomes one forty-six. Eight points gained, just by getting your cap table right.
Every claim needs proof.
Our Evidence Vault lets you upload pitch decks, connect GitHub, verify revenue through Stripe.
Each piece of evidence lifts your score -- from twenty percent confidence to ninety percent verified.
Your startup's value grows with you. Stripe for revenue data. GitHub for code activity. Pitch decks for investor readiness. Milestones for badge progress.
But we're just getting started.
Phase one, AI analysis -- that's live today. Phase two, evidence and validation. Phase three, dollar valuation engine. Phase four, full cap table management.
Then blockchain tokenization, investor matching, revenue tracking, and exit planning.
From idea to IPO -- one platform. Validate, build, prove, raise, and scale.
Australia has six hundred thousand private companies. Fifty thousand raise capital every year. Twenty-six hundred active startups. Fifteen thousand angel investors.
That's a three-point-two billion dollar addressable market in cap table and valuation tools alone.
Our pricing: first analysis free. Then one dollar per report. Founding fifty at forty-nine dollars for lifetime access. Growth plan at ninety-nine dollars a month.
Gross margins sit between eighty-eight and ninety-nine percent. AI costs under five dollars a day.
Unlike Carta, Pulley, or Qapita -- BlockID is built specifically for Australian founders.
AI valuation? Only us. AU-native compliance? Only us. Day zero to exit? Only us. Starting from one dollar? Only us. Blockchain equity? Only us.
ABN, ASIC, ESIC, R-and-D tax -- all baked in. Not an afterthought.
We're a lean, AI-first team. One founder plus nine AI agents -- CTO, CPO, CMO, CFO, COO, CRO, investor relations, media studio, and blockchain.
Fifty-four specialized skills. Built the full platform in nineteen days. Two hundred and seventy-two TypeScript files. Seventy API routes. Forty-one database tables.
Every feature ships in hours, not months.
And we're built for Australian compliance. ASIC registration. ESIC tax incentives. R-and-D tax offset. AU data residency.
Two hundred and fifty-two billion dollars invested in AI last year.
Ninety percent of those startups will fail.
Not because of bad ideas.
Because nobody helped them prove their value.
Until now.
Get your free SVI analysis at blockid.au.
Build it right. Build it valuable. Build it with BlockID.