Ninety percent of startups fail.
In Australia, three hundred and seventy thousand businesses closed last year alone.
Ninety-seven billion dollars poured into AI startups in twenty twenty-four alone.
But ninety percent of AI startups still fail. Average lifespan: eighteen months.
The problem? AI can build products. But it can't value them. It can't split equity. It can't prepare you for investors.
Manual valuation costs five to fifty thousand dollars and takes weeks.
BlockID changes this.
You describe your startup idea in plain text.
Our AI analyzes it across eight dimensions in real time.
Market. Product. Traction. Team. Cap table. Investor readiness. Legal. Vision.
AI-powered valuation in sixty seconds. From Day Zero.
One platform. Entire lifecycle.
Idea to MVP to fundraise to growth to exit.
Evidence vault. Cap table. Milestone badges. Living report. Every tool lifts your score.
A four-point-four trillion dollar global startup ecosystem. A three-point-two billion dollar cap table market.
Twenty-six hundred active Australian startups. And not one AI-native valuation platform.
AI builds products. BlockID builds businesses.
Try free: blockid.au