Ninety percent of startups fail.
Three hundred and seventy thousand Australian businesses closed last year.
Ninety-seven billion dollars poured into AI startups. Ninety percent still fail.
The gap: AI builds products. Nothing builds businesses.
I'm Do Van Long, founder of BlockID.
I've watched founders build incredible AI products, then struggle to value them, split equity fairly, or get investor-ready.
Everyone talks about building with AI. Nobody talks about building the business around it.
That's why I built BlockID. The platform that values startups from Day Zero.
Every founder faces three impossible questions.
First: How much is my startup worth? Manual valuation costs five to fifty thousand dollars and takes two to six weeks.
Second: How do I split equity? Forty-two percent of co-founder disputes destroy startups before they even launch.
Third: How do I get investor-ready? The average data room takes three to six weeks to prepare. Most founders never finish.
BlockID solves all three. Let me show you.
Here's BlockID in action.
You describe your startup idea in plain English.
BlockID detects your input type automatically.
Enter your email and hit 'Get My SVI'.
Now watch. Our AI agents go to work.
Researching your market. Scanning competitors. Evaluating your business model.
Generating your report.
And there it is. Your Startup Viability Index. A comprehensive AI-powered valuation.
Ten-page AI analysis. Market research. Competitor analysis. Business model evaluation. Actionable recommendations.
All in under a minute. What used to cost thousands and take weeks.
But here's what makes BlockID different. Every recommendation is actionable.
Click 'Build your cap table' and the tool opens right there.
Split equity between founders. Founder sixty percent, co-founder thirty, employee pool ten.
Complete the action and your score automatically increases.
Upload evidence. Pitch decks, revenue proof, GitHub repos. Each piece of verified evidence lifts your score.
Connect Stripe for revenue tracking. Connect GitHub for code activity. Your startup's value grows with you, automatically.
Your Living Report updates in real time. A dynamic dashboard that evolves as your startup evolves.
Earn milestone badges as you hit key startup milestones. Each one proves progress to investors.
But we're just getting started.
Phase One: AI Analysis. Live now. Proven. Working.
Phase Two: Evidence and Validation. Building your proof layer.
Phase Three: Dollar Valuation Engine. Real numbers, real confidence.
Phase Four: Full Cap Table Management.
Phase Five: Blockchain Tokenization on Cosmos.
Phase Six: Investor Matching and Fundraising.
Phase Seven: Revenue Tracking and Automatic Dividends.
Phase Eight: Growth Journal and Exit Preparation. Equity tokenized on blockchain. Automatic dividends. From idea to IPO, one platform.
The opportunity is massive.
A four-point-four trillion dollar global startup ecosystem. A three-point-two billion dollar cap table and valuation tools market.
Twenty-six hundred active Australian startups. Three hundred accelerators. Fifteen thousand angel investors.
And not one AI-native valuation platform built for Australia.
Start free. Your first analysis is on us. One dollar per report during early bird. Forty-nine dollars for the Founder plan: a hundred credits, lifetime access. Ninety-nine dollars per month for Growth: two hundred credits, everything included.
We're not just another SaaS tool. We're an AI-first company.
One founder supported by nine AI agent C-levels and twenty-three specialized skills. Shipping daily.
Built for Australian compliance from day one.
Carta is US-centric. Pulley starts at fundraise. Qapita covers Asia. BlockID starts at Day Zero. Before you've even incorporated.
Two hundred and fifty-two billion dollars invested in AI last year.
Ninety percent of those startups will fail.
Not because of bad ideas.
Because nobody helped them prove their value.
Until now.
BlockID dot au. Where AI meets startup valuation.
First analysis free. Start today.